[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
=Remnants of Gold=
(Adapted from Gu Long's
"Flying Eagle over the Great Land")
(The main characters
in this drama are fictional)
=Episode 12=
The Zhang lady.
You truly are no ordinary woman.
Who told you about me?
The Deputy
Military Commissioner of Liangzhou.
My family lived in Liangzhou.
I must've been seven years old.
One day,
my father, my brothers,
and I saw from afar
the General ascend
the Liangzhou city walls.
Clad in armor,
you looked like a god.
Back then, you guarded the Northwest
and protected
the twelve guards and four battalions.
To the people of Gansu, you were a god.
The 300,000 taels of gold...
Where is it hidden?
Zhang Luyao!
Move aside.
You can't enter the hall.
Is that the Commander-in-Chief's order
or General Ha's?
It makes no difference.
Trespassers
will be executed.
Zhang Luyao went inside?
Yes.
Move aside!
Stand back.
Get out of my way!
Within Gansu,
the General's orders are absolute.
God or ghost, anyone
who defies them will be killed.
Vice General Li
may not dare defy his orders,
but I'm not under his command.
You'll kill even a god?
Then try killing me!
The General is a god.
That's what my father used to say.
My father, Zhang Baoshi,
rarely spoke to me.
Because I was a daughter.
A daughter would eventually
marry and leave the family.
Once she left,
it was as if she'd never existed.
Where is the gold?
Why are you in such a hurry, General?
Hear me out.
I'll get to the gold.
My father often told my brothers
to be like you,
brave, upright, and responsible.
And yet,
you ordered Tie Futu to poison them.
Everyone dies eventually.
That alone is nothing.
If the General
had simply given the order
and demanded the lives
of my father and brothers,
they would have braved any danger
without a word of complaint.
I'm a woman under Liangzhou's rule.
I would have done the same.
Where exactly
are the 300,000 taels of gold?
Let me ask you one more question.
If you answer me truthfully,
I'll tell you where the gold is.
What is it? Ask.
In this life,
is it better to die
with wealth beyond measure
or to die with the respect of others?
People die for wealth,
just as birds die for food!
What do you believe in?
Ha!
[*"Believe" and "surname" sound alike]
So your surname is Ha.
I asked what you believe in.
In this life,
some believe in kindness,
some believe in courage,
some believe in keeping their word,
and some believe in honesty.
What do you believe in?
I am General Pingxi,
Commander-in-Chief of Gansu.
Where are the 300,000 taels of gold?
So you don't dare believe in anything.
That makes things much simpler.
If the Commander-in-Chief is the one
killing people for plunder,
a woman like me
wouldn't know what to do.
I am the Commander-in-Chief.
Where is the gold?
Here is my
Embroidered Uniform Guard token.
A seventh-rank
Embroidered Uniform Guard officer
has come to Gansu to investigate a case.
Appointed by the imperial court,
a seventh-rank officer has
come to Gansu to investigate a case!
Guan Shanyue, Commander-in-Chief of
Gansu, abused the law for personal gain,
colluded with bandits,
killed, and plundered.
All twelve guards and four battalions
under Gansu's command.
Are you soldiers of the imperial court
or soldiers of Guan Shanyue?
All land under heaven
belongs to the King.
That sand
reeks of the bone-dissolving water from
Qiku Gorge in the Qinling Mountains.
I checked it
when you went to fetch water.
The bones have dissolved,
but the lingering
deathly energy remains.
Your surname is Ha.
In the Northwest Great Desert,
who doesn't know
the Commander-in-Chief is Guan Shanyue?
You, surnamed Ha,
did you kill the General?
Where is the gold?
The General's guards will kill you.
The gold! Where is the gold?
Where is the gold?
Why should I tell you?
Are you planning to rebel?
Every one of you,
who dares rebel?
Do you?
Or do you?
Or you?
Open the door.
Move aside.
I'm going in, too.
Vice General Li.
Move aside!
I'm going in, too!
Vice General Li, please don't
make things difficult for us.
Deputy Yu has arrived.
Swallow it.
Where is Ha Bingzhong?
He went in to see the General.
Even the warriors
won't let you in, Vice General Li?
The General has given orders.
Trespassers will be executed.
The General is dead.
The General is dead!
How is that possible?
Deputy, don't speak such nonsense.
Do you have a death wish?
One of my men from the Liangzhou Guard
said the same thing as you,
Vice General Li.
Anyone who dares say the General is dead
will be executed.
An Embroidered Uniform Guard officer
just went in to see the General.
Move.
I, Yu Hou,
have failed the General.
Ha Bingzhong
issued false military orders
and ordered me to collude with bandits
and kill 27 members
of the Zhang family in Liangzhou.
The day before yesterday,
I knew the General was already dead,
yet I still
let greed get the better of me.
Deputy Yu,
what are you saying?
The General is dead.
Ha Bingzhong killed the attendant
who knew the truth
and buried the General
in the sand behind the residence.
For three months,
he claimed he was delivering medicine,
but in truth,
he was using poison
to dissolve the General's remains.
Nobody move.
Let me in.
I'll kill Ha Bingzhong,
or let him kill me.
Deputy.
Move aside.
Move aside!
Deputy.
Liangzhou Guard,
forward!
Coroner.
Don't move.
My friend,
save me
enough strength
to go in and kill Ha Bingzhong myself.
Draw your swords.
Deputy!
You're the General's personal guards.
You haven't seen him for three months.
Don't you miss the General?
I'll take you to see
the General's remains.
Move aside.
Move!
Anyone who stands in my way dies!
Move aside!
Open the door.
Let the Deputy
Military Commissioner of Liangzhou in.
General.
- General!
Zhang Luyao.
Zhang Luyao!
Zhang Luyao, it's me!
General.
Protect the General!
He's not the General!
The General is dead!
Ha Bingzhong!
Prepare to die!
Zhang Luyao, it's me!
I'm Pu Ying!
I don't want to kill you,
and I don't want to die
at anyone else's hands.
Aren't you immune to all poisons?
Kill me, and you won't
have to suffer anymore.
Kill me!
Kill me.
Zhang Luyao.
Zhang Luyao!
It hurts!
Deputy!
General!
This isn't the General!
Ha Bingzhong
has brought chaos to Gansu.
You killed the wrong man!
Zhang Luyao!
I'm Pu Ying!
Let go.
Let go!
You want to see the General?
I'll take you
to see him.
This way,
the General is still here.
Deputy.
Deputy Yu.
Zhang Luyao.
It's me.
Yu Hou.
This is where we part.
Zhang Luyao.
Officer.
Where's Ha Bingzhong?
Dead.
Don't touch her!
Officer said not to touch her.
Coroner.
Go check on her.
Is she still alive?
Don't move.
Deputy.
I know where she wants to go.
I'll return to the Capital and report
on what happened in Gansu.
Officer,
what are your orders?
Prepare a carriage.
Yes.
On this journey west,
whether I live or die,
I will never return.
Everyone at
the Zhang Escort Agency is dead.
You are responsible
for the people of Liangzhou.
I'll leave
the agency's property deed to you.
For military or civilian use,
do with it as you see fit.
You won't return even if you survive?
Do you have family in Gansu, Deputy?
The Commander-in-Chief
was like a father and brother to me.
Were you the one
who poisoned the 27 members
of my family?
No.
I believe you.
I'll leave the silver bell
with you, too.
Officer Pu was poisoned
by the feed for less than an hour.
His frenzy gradually subsided.
The ancient Western Sichuan bell
can calm the mind.
It can help those overcome
by panic and frenzy
calm down until their strength is spent.
Why give it to me?
Your heart is full of turmoil, Deputy.
Don't you need it?
My heart is perfectly calm.
Deep down,
I've had many dark thoughts,
but I've never dared act on them.
Being tired of the great desert
and wanting to go south
isn't a dark thought.
I've never met anyone like you.
After daybreak,
we'll go our separate ways.
We'll never meet again in this life.
That's all?
You're a good man.
Good people should live a little longer.
I never thought it would end like this.
I'm going to sleep.
Have a safe journey
at daybreak, Officer.
We'll bury this lady here?
That's all we can do.
You'll be buried here too when you die?
When I die,
I want to be buried at Wusu Sea.
Bancha said
there's no better place
in the world than Wusu Sea.
How good is it?
It's like heaven.
Yan.
Go back to Mount Pingfeng.
Who's that man on horseback?
Zhang Luyao hasn't come out
of the carriage for two days.
Even someone alive would be dead by now.
If she's dead, why not bury her?
Where are they
taking her in that carriage?
Wusu Sea lies to the north.
Do you think the gold might be there?
How much gold can one carriage carry?
Zhang Luyao is dead.
Does that upset you?
Yan, I was wrong.
Back in Ganzhou,
I shouldn't have said
I couldn't let her go.
You didn't say that. I asked you.
Yan.
I was wrong.
If you keep looking at me like that,
I'm going to get angry.
Bancha.
Are we at Wusu Sea yet?
If we're there,
why are the horses still moving?
Then I need to pee.
Why are you still calling me Bancha?
Because you're Bancha.
I need to get off the horse and pee.
What a nuisance.
Hold it.
I can't.
I said hold it.
Shut up.
Stay away from the water.
I'm going to pee.
That's why you need
to stay away from the water.
Go.
The farther away, the better.
The water isn't deep.
You can cross.
I said you can cross.
They can't speak.
My name is Tang Zheng.
(Preview of the Next Episode)
Zhang Luyao wanted
to be buried at Wusu Sea.
So you're waiting here for her.
You're taking her back to the Tang Clan?
Cremate her.
Eat slowly.
She's a human being, too!
=Remnants of Gold=